Louis de Pol

Manchester M4 louisdepol8_n6e@indeedemail.com +44 7786 517944

I am 25 years old and looking for regular full time bar work, ideally around 35-40 hours per week, though I can be flexible. I have worked on and off in the hospitality industry since leaving school, and consider myself an experienced cocktail bartender, having created menus and worked many high-volume weekends! I love learning and new experiences, and always try and keep a calm and positive outlook, on both work and life. Outside of work, I love music, and have played live and released various things over the past decade, football and going to nice restaurants and bars.

Personal Details

Driver's License: Cars

Eligible to work in the UK: Yes

Highest Level of Education: A-Level or equivalent

Work Experience

Cocktail Bartender

Mala - Manchester June 2022 to February 2023

At Mala, I had various responsibilities, including coming up with menu drinks (I had two in the top 5 bestsellers of the year), prepping pre-mix batches for the weekend, changing kegs and gas canisters, keeping the bar clean and organised, and along with the bar supervisor making sure that all other daily and weekly prep was done to a high standard and on time. Because of the target audience of Mala being very big into social media and the 'instagrammability' of their drinks, my presentation and garnishing improved greatly, and I also learnt techniques I hadn't used before, such as flavouring vodka and spicing rum.

Cocktail Bartender

Elnecot - Manchester April 2021 to March 2022

At Elnecot, I got used to a fast and busy work environment very quickly, becoming a key member of the bar team during my time. My responsibilities included coming up with new cocktails to put on the menu and also for weekly specials, maintaining a clean and well stocked bar, making several different types of drinks quickly and well, ranging from coffees, cocktails, beers and wines, receiving and putting away deliveries and arranging the cellar, changing barrels, running food and serving customers. At Elnecot I showed I was able to work with speciality or premium ingredients and make them into great tasting and great looking drinks. I was also referred to by the bar manager as 'head bartender', leaving me in charge when he wasn't in, teaching newer members of staff skills they may not yet have, and asking advice on various admin parts of his job.

Customer Service Advisor

Concentrix (HSBC, RAC) - Salford September 2019 to September 2020

I worked on two different campaigns in my time at Concentrix, HSBC and RAC. For HSBC I was in a fast paced environment where calls on a wide range of queries would come in and I had to solve the customer's problem in a quick and friendly way. It gave me experience in interacting with difficult or unhappy customers - building on skills I learnt in my prior job as a pub supervisor - thinking on my feet, and towards the end of my time there, helping newer members of my team when they had issues on their calls. At RAC I worked in inbound sales, and the main skill I learnt here was identifying a specific customer's needs and directing them toward the product that suited that best.

Supervisor

Lass O'Gowrie - Manchester June 2018 to August 2019

After two months at the Lass I was promoted from bartender to supervisor, which gave me more responsibility at work for the first time. I learned how to delegate, to take on a role where I am training others or helping them improve their own skills, and to do day to day tasks such as counting the till, cleaning the lines and placing and receiving orders.

Bartender

Boulters Lock Restaurant - Maidenhead October 2017 to May 2018

At Boulters my responsibility was the restaurant bar. I worked every sunday morning, which meant serving a lot of customers coffees in a short time frame, and received training on this as well. As well as this, I also got cocktail training for the first time and would occasionally go on the floor as a waiter in busy periods.

Bartender/Waiter

The Golden Ball - Maidenhead April 2016 to August 2017

The Golden Ball was my first full time job. As well as learning how the hospitality industry worked, I showed I was able to learn quickly, work both under supervision and independently, and to work effectively as a part of a team. I was trained informally here by other staff on most aspects of being a barista, bartender and waiter.

Education

A Levels in Music, French and English Literature

Henley College

September 2013 to Present

English Language, English Literature, Maths, Physics, Chemistry, French, German, Music, History

John Hampden Grammar School September 2008 to June 2013